<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Products &#8211; Noveny life</title>
	<atom:link href="https://novenylife.com/shop/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://novenylife.com</link>
	<description>Noveny life Best Product</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 09:17:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://novenylife.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Noveny-logo-75x75.png</url>
	<title>Products &#8211; Noveny life</title>
	<link>https://novenylife.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Noveny Sweet Almond Cold-Pressed Oil</title>
		<link>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-sweet-almond-cold-pressed-oil/</link>
				<comments>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-sweet-almond-cold-pressed-oil/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 10:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartcoders]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://novenylife.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=592</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Noveny Sweet Almond Cold-Pressed Oil, 100% Pure &#38; Natural For Face Care, Nail Care, Hair, Lip care and Baby Massage (15ml, 30ml, 120ml)</p>
<ol>
<li>FACE CARE: Almond oil has antioxidant properties that fight wrinkles and reduce sagging of the skin. Massage 2 drops of almond oil on face and under the eyes before going to sleep every night.</li>
<li>BABY MASSAGE: Almond oil is the best massage oils for babies and adults, almond oil is rich in antioxidants, proteins and Omega 3. Use just 5 drops of almond oil and massage.</li>
<li>HAIR CARE: Almond oil helps in promoting hair growth and it nourishes and strengthens your hair. Warm 1 tbsp of Almond oil and massage it on the scalp every night to nourish hair and make it stronger.</li>
<li>LIP CARE: Almond oil massage on lips will rejuvenate the dead cells, prevent chapped lips and keep them moisturized. Apply 2 drops of almond oil on lips for protection, care and nourishment.</li>
<li>NAIL CARE: Almond oil helps to protect cuticles of the nails and keeps our nails healthy. Use 3 drops of almond oil on nails &#38; cuticles for nourishment, protection and health.</li>
<li>USE AS A MASSAGE OIL: Almond Oil is one of the best massage oil for babies &#38; adults.</li>
<li>Cold Pressed process retains all the goodness as the extraction process does not use heat or harmful chemicals.</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-sweet-almond-cold-pressed-oil/">Noveny Sweet Almond Cold-Pressed Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-sweet-almond-cold-pressed-oil/">Noveny Sweet Almond Cold-Pressed Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-sweet-almond-cold-pressed-oil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Noveny Onion Seed Cold-Pressed Oil</title>
		<link>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-onion-seed-cold-pressed-oil/</link>
				<comments>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-onion-seed-cold-pressed-oil/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 10:21:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartcoders]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://novenylife.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=554</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Noveny Onion Seed Cold-Pressed Oil, 100% Pure &#38; Natural For Skin Care, Hair Care, Cold &#38; Cough and Insect Repellent (15ml, 30ml, 120ml)</p>
<ol>
<li>HAIR CARE: Onion seed Oil nourishes and stimulates scalp and helps in encouraging the growth of new hair. Mix 3 drops of onion seed oil in 10 ml of coconut or olive, and apply on scalp and massage.</li>
<li>NOURISHES THE SKIN: Onion Seed Oil keeps the skin healthy and fresh and clears the face off acne and fungus, making s fresh and pretty. Add 3 drops of onion seed oil to 2 tbsp of carrier oil and massage on skin and face helps increase blood circulation and improves the overall appearance of your skin.</li>
<li>FOR COLD &#38; COUGH: Onion seed oil is useful in clearing the throat and the nasal tract of the mucus and congestion. Apply 5 drops of onion seed oil on chest and rub if suffering from cold.</li>
<li>HEALS WOUNDS: Onion seed oil has anti-bacterial and anti-fungal properties that help to heal wounds. Apply 3 drops of onion seed oil on wound so as to cure infection and heal wounds.</li>
<li>USE AS A INSECT REPELLENT: Onion Seed oil is the best used as a insect repellent as well as a form of sting treatment. Apply 5 drops of onion seed oil on open skin areas so as to reduce the pain caused from honeybee stings and insect bites.</li>
<li>CONTROL BLOOD SUGAR LEVELS: Adding 2 drops of onion seed oil to food helps in controlling blood sugar levels.</li>
<li>Cold Pressed process retains all the goodness as the extraction process does not use heat or harmful chemicals.</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-onion-seed-cold-pressed-oil/">Noveny Onion Seed Cold-Pressed Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-onion-seed-cold-pressed-oil/">Noveny Onion Seed Cold-Pressed Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-onion-seed-cold-pressed-oil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Noveny Moroccan Argan Cold-Pressed Oil</title>
		<link>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-moroccan-argan-cold-pressed-oil/</link>
				<comments>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-moroccan-argan-cold-pressed-oil/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 13:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartcoders]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://novenylife.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=533</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Noveny Moroccan Argan Cold-Pressed Oil, 100% Pure &#38; Natural For Acne Control, Anti-aging, Hair Care, Lip &#38; Nail Care (15ml, 30ml, 120ml)</p>
<ol>
<li>HAIR CARE: Argan oil nourishes hair follicles and promotes hair growth.It is good for curly hair and manages frizz. Apply 3 drops to freshly washed and towel-dried hair to manage frizz. Good for curly hair.</li>
<li>ACNE CONTROL: Argan oil has anti-oxidant properties helps to control acne and keep your skin healthy. Apply 3 drops on face in smooth circular motion to moisturize skin so as to control acne.</li>
<li>ANTI-AGING: Argan Oil has anti-oxident properties that combats the signs of ageing. Apply 2-3 drops on face and neck to massage regularly before going to bed.</li>
<li>NAIL CARE: Argan oil helps to protect cuticles of the nails and keeps our nails healthy. For nail health, apply 3 drops over nails, cuticles and finer skin and massage.</li>
<li>LIP CARE: Argan oil helps to moisturize and soften the lips and keep them from being damaged due to dehydration. Gently massage 2 drops onto your lip to keep them soft and moistured.</li>
<li>HAIR CONDITIONING: Apply 5 drops of Argan oil to freshly washed and towel-dried hair to manage frizz.</li>
<li>Cold Pressed process retains all the goodness as the extraction process does not use heat or harmful chemicals.</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-moroccan-argan-cold-pressed-oil/">Noveny Moroccan Argan Cold-Pressed Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-moroccan-argan-cold-pressed-oil/">Noveny Moroccan Argan Cold-Pressed Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-moroccan-argan-cold-pressed-oil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Noveny Lemongrass Essential Oil</title>
		<link>https://novenylife.com/product/lemongrass-oil/</link>
				<comments>https://novenylife.com/product/lemongrass-oil/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 12:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartcoders]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://novenylife.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=517</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Noveny Lemongrass Essential Oil, 100% Pure &#38; Natural For Face Care, Hair care, Insect repellent, Massage &#38; Aroma diffusers (15ml, 30ml, 120ml)</p>
<ol>
<li>FACE CLEANING: Lemongrass oil has antiseptic properties that cleanses the pores, remove the toxins and dirt from the skin. Mix 2 drops of lemongrass oil in 5ml of coconut oil to cleanse the pores and make skin look good.</li>
<li>HAIR CARE: Lemongrass Oil contains anti-fungal properties that helps in treating scalp infection and helps in reducing dandruff. Add 5 drops of lemongrass oil to 5 tsp of coconut oil. Gently massage and leave it for 1 hour before washing to get relief from dandruff.</li>
<li>REFRESHING AROMA: Lemongrass has mood enhancing fragrance, lemongrass oil is used popularly in aromatherapy and as a home fragrance. Add 10 drops per 200 ml water in a diffuser for refreshing mood.</li>
<li>INSECT REPELLENT: Lemongrass Oil has a fresh lemony and earthy aroma and used to repel insects and mosquitoes naturally. Mix 15 drops into water in a spray bottle to get rid of insects.</li>
<li>HOUSE CLEANING : Lemongrass oil is used as an air freshener.Its aroma helps create a refreshing atmosphere at home. Mix 20 drops into water in a spray bottle for spraying at home. It also helps in cleaning and makes air fresh.</li>
<li>BODY MASSAGE: Lemongrass oil is used in massage therapy. Blend 3 drops of oil in carrier oil for relaxing massage therapy.</li>
<li>Always use diluted essential oils before use as they are highly concentrated and should be handled with caution.Refer Noveny's Essential oil dilution guide or consult our experts.</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/lemongrass-oil/">Noveny Lemongrass Essential Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/lemongrass-oil/">Noveny Lemongrass Essential Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://novenylife.com/product/lemongrass-oil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Noveny Herbal Eucalyptus Essential Oil</title>
		<link>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-eucalyptus-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/</link>
				<comments>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-eucalyptus-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 08:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartcoders]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://novenylife.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=474</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Noveny Herbal Eucalyptus Essential Oil, 100% Pure &#38; Natural For Acne control, Hair Care, Room diffuser, For Cold &#38; Cough and Pain Relief (15ml, 30ml, 120ml)</p>
<ol>
<li>ACNE CONTROL &#38; FACE CARE: Eucalyptus oil has antibacterial and anti-inflammatory properties that helps in controlling Acne. Mix 2 drops of Eucalyptus anti-bacterial oil with a little water or moisturizer to get rid of acne.</li>
<li>FOR COLD &#38; COUGH: Eucalyptus oil is useful in clearing the throat and the nasal tract of the mucus and congestion. Apply 5 drops of eucalyptus oil on chest and rub to get relief from cold &#38; cough.</li>
<li>HAIR CARE: Eucalyptus Oil helps in fighting against dandruff with its anti-fungal properties and keeps lice away as well.Mix 3 drops of Eucalyptus oil into carrier oil and gently massage on the scalp. Wash after an hour.</li>
<li>REFRESHING AROMA: Eucalyptus oil has a minty smell with a hint of honey. It has pungent, intoxicating scent. Add 5-10 drops of Eucalyptus oil to per 200ml water for a room diffuser.</li>
<li>MUSCLES PAIN RELIEF: Eucalyptus oil is antispasmodic and gives relief to strained muscles. It re-energizes the muscles and helps in faster healing. Mix 5 drops of Eucalyptus oil with 1-2 tsp of a carrier oil for a relaxing massage and muscles pain.</li>
<li>MIX WITH CARRIER OILS: Mix 2 drops of Carrot Seed Oil with carrier oil to use on hair ,face and muscle pain relief.</li>
<li>Always use diluted essential oils before use as they are highly concentrated and should be handled with caution.Refer Noveny's Essential oil dilution guide or consult our experts.</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-eucalyptus-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/">Noveny Herbal Eucalyptus Essential Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-eucalyptus-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/">Noveny Herbal Eucalyptus Essential Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-eucalyptus-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Noveny Therapeutic Lemon Essential Oil</title>
		<link>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-lemon-essential-oil/</link>
				<comments>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-lemon-essential-oil/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 06:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartcoders]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://novenylife.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=454</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Noveny Therapeutic Lemon Essential Oil, 100% Pure &#38; Natural For Acne Control, Face Cleaning, Anti-aging, Massage and Aroma Diffuser (15ml, 30ml, 120ml)</p>
<ol>
<li>ANTI-AGING: Lemon Oil helps in anti-aging effects.It reduces scars and any other skin trauma and makes skin look smooth.Add 2-3 drops of lemon oil to 2 tbsp of facial cream to help remove dead skin cells and make skin look lighten.</li>
<li>FACE CARE &#38; ACNE CONTROL: Lemon oil has antibacterial and anti-inflammatory properties that helps in controlling acne and removes dead skin cells.Use 2-3 drops of lemon oil and apply on face for excessive oil and to make face acne free.</li>
<li>REFRESHING AROMA: Lemon Essential Oil has a powerfully fresh traditional lemon fragrance that is quite energizing and uplifting.Add 5-10 drops of lemon oil to diffuser for a room diffuser.</li>
<li>USE AS A FACE CLEANSER: Lemon oil is used as a face cleanseras it reduces excessive oil on the skin.Add a few drops of the oil to facial cleanser to help remove dead skin cells.</li>
<li>NECK MASSAGE: Lemon oil is used in neck massage as its soothing and cooling properties gives relief to pain.Mix 2-3 drops of lemon oil and 2-3 drops of coconut oil and massage on the back of the neck to get relief.</li>
<li>USE IN DRINKING WATER: Add 2 drops in 1 glass of warm water for gargle to make throat feel relax.</li>
<li>Always use diluted essential oils before use as they are highly concentrated and should be handled with caution.Refer Noveny's Essential oil dilution guide or consult our experts.</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-lemon-essential-oil/">Noveny Therapeutic Lemon Essential Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-lemon-essential-oil/">Noveny Therapeutic Lemon Essential Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-lemon-essential-oil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Noveny Sweet Orange Essential Oil</title>
		<link>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-orange-essential-oil/</link>
				<comments>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-orange-essential-oil/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 05:37:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartcoders]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://novenylife.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=428</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Noveny Sweet Orange Essential Oil, 100% Pure &#38; Natural For Acne control, Skin Lightening, hair, Lip care and Aroma Diffusers (15ml, 30ml, 120ml)</p>
<ol>
<li>ACNE CONTROL &#38; FACE CARE: Orange Oil has antibacterial and anti-inflammatory properties helps in controlling Acne.Dilute 4 drops of orange oil in 3 tsp of aloe vera gel and apply for acne relief.</li>
<li>HAIR CARE &#38; GROWTH: Orange oil helps in promoting hair growth and prevents from fungal infection.Add about 40-50 drops of orange oil to 250ml conditioner bottle. Mix with regular shampoo and cleanses.</li>
<li>REFRESHING AROMA: The fresh, tangy scent of orange oil invigorates and sharpens your senses.Diffuse at home, or add to shower gel for a stress-reducing, refreshing and uplifting citrus aroma.</li>
<li>LIP CARE: Orange oil provides hydration and locks moisture for soft and nourished lips.Mix 1/2 of cocoa and mango butter and add 4 drops of Orange oil to keep lips soft and nourished.</li>
<li>SKIN LIGHTENING: Orange oil can aid in skin lightening since it reduces inflammation and treats dry skin.Mix 4 drops of orange oil in 1 tsp of coconut or almond oil and massage for skin lightening.</li>
<li>MASSAGE FOR GLOWING SKIN: Mix 3 drops of orange oil in oils like (coconut oil, jojoba oil or almond oil) for skin lightening and massage for skin benefits.</li>
<li>Always use diluted essential oils before use as they are highly concentrated and should be handled with caution.Refer Noveny's Essential oil dilution guide or consult our experts.</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-orange-essential-oil/">Noveny Sweet Orange Essential Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-orange-essential-oil/">Noveny Sweet Orange Essential Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-orange-essential-oil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Noveny Australian Tea Tree Essential Oil</title>
		<link>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-australian-tea-tree-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/</link>
				<comments>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-australian-tea-tree-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 10:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartcoders]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://novenylife.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=411</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Noveny Australian Tea Tree Essential Oil, 100% Pure &#38; Natural For Acne control, Hair care, Nail &#38; toe infection, Home Cleaning and Aroma Diffusers (15ml, 30ml, 120ml)</p>
<ol>
<li>ACNE CONTROL: Tea Tree Oil has antibacterial and anti-inflammatory properties helps in controlling Acne. Mix 2 drops of tea tree oil with 1 tsp coconut oil for acne prone skin.</li>
<li>NAIL &#38; TOE INFECTION: Tea Tree Oil has an excellent anti-microbial and anti-inflammatory agent that helps in treating skin and nail infections.Mix 5 drops of tea tree oil with 5 ml of almond oil. Apply using a cotton ball on the infected area.</li>
<li>HAIR CARE: Tea Tree Oil helps in fighting against dandruff with its anti-fungal properties and keeps lice away as well.Mix 5 drops of tea tree oil with 10 ml in any of coconut, jojoba, almond oil and apply to scalp and hair.</li>
<li>REFRESHING AROMA: Tea Tree Oil is used in diffuser as it naturally combat the odor as well as freshen the air.Add 5-10 drops per 200ml water in a diffuser to freshen up the air.</li>
<li>CLEAN &#38; TIDY HOME: Tea Tree oil has anti-microbial and disinfectant properties that kill the germs and pathogens.Mix 10-20 drops to 1 cup of water and spray to get home rid of germs &#38; bed bugs.</li>
<li>REMOVES LICE: Mix 1 drop of tea tree oil per 1 oz. of the regular shampoo to remove lice.</li>
<li>Always use diluted essential oils before use as they are highly concentrated and should be handled with caution.Refer Noveny's Essential oil dilution guide or consult our experts.</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-australian-tea-tree-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/">Noveny Australian Tea Tree Essential Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-australian-tea-tree-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/">Noveny Australian Tea Tree Essential Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-australian-tea-tree-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Noveny Carrot Seed Essential Oil</title>
		<link>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-carrot-seed-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/</link>
				<comments>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-carrot-seed-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 13:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartcoders]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://novenylife.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=351</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Noveny Carrot Seed <a href="https://novenylife.com/">Essential Oil</a> 100% Pure &#38; Natural For Skin Care, Skin lightening, Hair Care, Face Care, Anti-aging &#38; Aroma Diffusers (15ml, 30ml, 120ml)</p>
<ol>
<li>HAIR CARE &#38; DANDRUFF CONTROL: Carrot Seed oil helps in promoting hair growth and fights dandruff. Mix 4 to 5 drops of carrot seed oil in 10 ml of hair oil for healthy hair growth.</li>
<li>SKIN LIGHTENING: Carrot Seed oil can aid in skin lightening since it reduces inflammation and treats dry skin. Apply the mixture of 2 drops of rose oil, 4 drops of carrot seed oil and 1 tbsp. of Skin Mousse for skin lightening.</li>
<li>ANTI-AGING: Carrot Seed Oil helps in anti-aging effects.It reduces scars and any other skin trauma and makes skin look smooth.Mix 3 drops of carrot seed, 2 drops of lavender with 1 tbsp of Jojoba oil and 2 tbsp of aloevera gel and massage gently on face.</li>
<li>REFRESHING AROMA: Carrot Seed Oil is used in diffuser for its earthy and refreshing aroma which reduces anxiety and stress.Boil 2-3 cups of water and add 5-10 drops of Carrot Seed oil for homemade diffuser.</li>
<li>THERAPEUTIC BATH: Carrot Seed Oil boosts the therapeutic quality of a bath with its sweetly rich and grounding scent.Mix 5-10 drops of Carrot Seed Oil with 1 cup of Dead Sea Salt and pour it under warm running water inside a bathtub.</li>
<li>HAIR GROWTH: Mix 6 drops of Carrot Seed Oil, 4 drops Sandalwood Oil, 2 drops of Carrier Oil, 2 drops Cedarwood Oil, and 1 Tbsp. of Jojoba Oil for hair growth.</li>
<li>Always use diluted essential oils before use as they are highly concentrated and should be handled with caution.Refer Noveny's Essential oil dilution guide or consult our experts.</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-carrot-seed-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/">Noveny Carrot Seed Essential Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-carrot-seed-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/">Noveny Carrot Seed Essential Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-carrot-seed-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Noveny Bulgarian Lavender Essential Oil</title>
		<link>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-bulgarian-lavender-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/</link>
				<comments>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-bulgarian-lavender-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 07:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartcoders]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://novenylife.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=70</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Noveny Bulgarian Lavender Essential Oil 100% Pure &#38; Natural For Skin, Hair, Face, Body Massage &#38; Aroma Diffuser (15ml, 30ml, 120ml)</p>
<ol>
<li style="text-align: left;">RELAXING SLEEP: Add 2 drops of lavender oil on your pillow for a restful sleep. For headache relief, dilute a few drops with a carrier oil (coconut, almond oil etc.) and apply across the temples and forehead. Or add a drop to a tissue paper and gently inhale.</li>
<li style="text-align: left;">ACNE CONTROL &#38; FACE CARE: Lavender oil works to kill bacteria, prevent and heal acne breakouts. Add 2-3 drops of lavender oil in 10 ml of jojoba oil and use as a moisturizer on a clean face. Reduces red, inflamed pimples &#38; acne.</li>
<li style="text-align: left;">HAIR CARE: Lavender oil helps in promoting hair growth and fights dandruff. Mix 4-5 drops of lavender oil with coconut oil and massage your hair and scalp.</li>
<li style="text-align: left;">BODY MASSAGE: Lavender oil is the perfect addition to massage oil to de-stress and relieve tired, tense muscles.Blend 4-5 drops with a carrier oil of your choice for a relaxing massage.</li>
<li style="text-align: left;">THERAPEUTIC BATH: Use 2-3 drops of Lavender Oil regularly in your water while taking bath.</li>
<li style="text-align: left;">REFRESHING AROMA: Lavender oil used in diffusers as its smell so good to reduce stress &#38; anxiety.Use 2-3 drops of lavender oil in diffusers to make the surrounding aromatic with soothing Lavender aroma.</li>
<li style="text-align: left;">Always use diluted essential oils before use as they are highly concentrated and should be handled with caution.Refer Noveny's Essential oil dilution guide or consult our experts.</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-bulgarian-lavender-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/">Noveny Bulgarian Lavender Essential Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-bulgarian-lavender-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/">Noveny Bulgarian Lavender Essential Oil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://novenylife.com">Noveny life</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://novenylife.com/product/noveny-bulgarian-lavender-essential-oil-100-pure-natural/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
